https://www.arkahsd.com/page/privacy-policy.html

Toggle navigation 6171 Balboa AvenueSan Diego, CA 92111858-277-3665Request AppointmentPetlyOnline PharmacyRequest AppointmentePetHealthOnline Pharmacy
Home
AboutAbout Us Our Team Our Patients Clinic Tour
Patient CenterClient Forms Payment Options Videos
ServicesPet Services Dental Care Emergency Care
ShoppingCoupons Home Delivery Pharmacy
Testimonials Contact Us
Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy governs the manner in which our website collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the this website ("Site").Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationWe may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:To run and operate our SiteWe may need your information display content on the Site correctly.To run different marketing campaigns including retargeting display adsTo improve customer serviceInformation you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.To improve our SiteWe may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site featureTo send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.How we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.Sharing your personal informationWe may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.Electronic newslettersIf User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.Third party websitesUsers may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licencors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.Changes to this privacy policyWe have the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.This document was last updated on May 11, 2015
InformationAddress: 6171 Balboa Avenue
San Diego, CA 92111 Phone: 858-277-3665 E-mail: Send a Message
Useful LinksServices Meet The Team Online Forms Privacy Policy Office HoursDayMorningAfternoonMonday8:00 - 11:30am1:00 - 5:00Tuesday8:00 - 11:30am1:00 - 5:00Wednesday8:00 - 11:30am1:00 - 5:00Thursday8:00 - 11:30am1:00 - 5:00Friday8:00 - 11:30am1:00 - 5:00Saturday8:00 - 3:00SundayClosed
Powered by
Form submitted successfully! You are missing required fields. Dynamic Error Description There was an error processing this form.
Close
Experience Excellence in Veterinary Care
CellHomeWork
DogCat
JanuaryFebruaryMarchAprilMayJuneJulyAugustSeptemberOctoberNovemberDecember 12345678910111213141516171819202122232425262728293031 8:00am9:00am10:00am11:00am12:00pm1:00pm2:00pm3:00pm4:00pm5:00pm We will review your request and confirm your appointment as soon as possible. Form submitted successfully! You are missing required fields. Dynamic Error Description There was an error processing this form.
Close
Online PharmacyTo refill a previous online pharmacy orderclick hereTo visit the Online Pharmacyclick here
Close
× Login
Forgot Password? OR
Sign in with Facebook Sign in with Google
Looking to create an account ?
